<!--
  @author Reika Kalseki
  
  Copyright 2018
  
  All rights reserved.
  Distribution of the software in any form is only allowed with
  explicit, prior permission from the owner.
-->
<?xml version="1.0"?>
<machines>
	<adjacency>
		<desc>
			Многие вещи, которые вы создавали, если и не были полным провалом, то точно имели какой-то существенный недостаток. Конечно, вы пытались их улучшить, но чаще всего это было либо невозможно, либо ужасно дорого; поэтому вы нашли способ повлиять на механизм извне. Ядра, что вы создали, сильно помогут вам в развитии. Разные цвета, естественно, дадут разный эффект.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Каждое ядро имеет 8 уровней.
			Каждый следующий уровень мощнее предыдущего.
		</note>
		<black>
			Есть ли кристальные усилители, или нет, ваша сеть сильно перегружена. Вы пока не нашли способ улучшить ваши пилоны, но что если попробовать снизить нагрузку?
		</black>
		<red>
			Вам приснился сон, что двигатели, охлаждаемые водой, внезапно взорвались, оставив от вашей базы лишь большой кратер. Это натолкнуло вас на мысль, что ценные вещи нуждаются в особой защите...
		</red>
		<green>
			Вы нашли много способов ускорить рост растений, но многие из них очень неэффективны. Кажется, вы придумали нечто, что может положить конец вашим поискам.
		</green>
		<brown>
			Руда - та вещь, которую вы совсем не замечаете, пока она у вас не закончатся. Вы потратили около ста листов бумаги, рассуждая на тему того, как ускорить добычу ценных минералов. И кажется, вы нашли способ превращать самый обычный камень в руду, что позволит вам больше никогда не спускаться в шахту.
		</brown>
		<purple>
			Как ни странно, у этого ядра нет прямого назначения. Оно просто улучшает всё вокруг себя. Что бы это не означало, вы надеетесь, что эксперементы окажутся положительными.
		</purple>
		<cyan>
			Кристальные резервуары - полезная вещь, однако бывает так, что они находятся в закрытом помещении, а места, чтобы повысить вместимость резервуара, в нём больше нет. Похоже, вы наконец нашли решение этой проблемы.
		</cyan>
		<lightgray>
			Вы уже давно поняли, что находясь рядом с определёнными кристаллами, вы можете получать опыт. Однако этот процесс занимает много времени... Но что, если кто-то или что-то могло находится там вместо вас?
		</lightgray>
		<gray>
			Всегда хотели перемещать блоки не перемещая их? Скорее всего нет, но теперь вы можете.
		</gray>
		<pink>
			Существующие способы защиты вашего дома уже недостаточно хороши, поэтому им требуется модернизация. Это ядро не подпустит ни одного крипера к вашему дому!
		</pink>
		<lime>
			У многих структур с зоной действия есть один существенный недостаток: радиус этой самой зоны. Это ядро позволяет сильно увеличить дальность действия любых конструкций.
		</lime>
		<yellow>
			В последнее время, особенно сильно ощущается проблема нехватки энергии. Поэтому вы создали ядро, способное сильно увеличить энергию, создаваемую реактором и, возможно, другими генераторами.
		</yellow>
		<lightblue>
			Как вы уже поняли, светло-голубая энергия чаще всего ассоциируется с временем и его управлением. Концентрируя эту энергию, вам удалось создать ядро, в радиусе действия которого время течёт значительно быстрее.
		</lightblue>
		<magenta>
			Часто многие блоки изнашиваются и ломаются. Вы, конечно, можете просто починить их, но не лучше ли будет создать вещь, которая будет сама чинить предметы вокруг?
		</magenta>
		<orange>
			Перегрев реактора - существенная проблема. Контроллер, что вы создавали, оказался неэффективен, поэтому после недельной головоломки, вы придумали это ядро, рассеивающее тепло вокруг.
		</orange>
		<white>
			Стабильность - это хорошо. Однако существующая система крафта так не считает. Это ядро поможет вам переубедить её.
		</white>
	</adjacency>
	<guardian>
		<desc>
			Как ни странно, вокруг бегает много воров, только и желающий чего-нибудь у кого-нибудь украсть. Вы - не исключение. Конечно, можно наложить защитное заклинание, но они неэффективны, и у них ограниченный радиус действия. На помощь приходит защитный камень, который не позволяет ворам проникнуть в ваши сундуки или украсть ваши ресурсы.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Не позволяет ставить или ломать блоки, а также открывать интерфейсы в радиусе %d блоков.

			Владельцы и администраторы - исключение.
			Владелец также может использовать /guardstone add/remove &#60;Игрок&#62;, чтобы открыть/закрыть доступ другим игрокам. <!-- The &# tags are for angle brackets. Do not touch those. -->
		</note>
	</guardian>
	<stand>
		<desc>
			Чтобы создавать более сложные предметы на магическом верстаке, потребуется расширить стандартную 3х3 сетку крафта. Для этого можно использовать магические пьедесталы, встроенные в конструкцию магической комнаты. Не забудьте приподнять внешнее кольцо на один блок выше внутреннего.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</stand>
	<telepump>
		<desc>
			У вас уже есть различные насосы и помпы для переноса различных жидкостей, однако иногда, они располагаются не большими морями, а маленькими озёрами по всей карте. Быстрее будет перенести всё вёдрами, чем постоянно переносить насос от озера к озеру. Но вы нашли решение этой проблемы: Телепортирующая помпа. Она, используя энергию движения, осушает все озёра вокруг, что значительно ускоряет сбор жидкости.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Перед выкачиванием, сканирует территорию вокруг.
		</note>
	</telepump>
	<miner>
		<desc>
			Большую часть времени в шахте вы копаете ненужный булыжник и подобные породы, и это проблема. Конечно, есть всеразличные карьеры, но они тоже добывают в основном мусор. На помощь приходит минеральный экстрактор. Он способен точно определять руды и выкапывать их в довольно большом радиусе, что намного удобнее того же минерального обогатителя.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Перед добычей, сканирует территорию вокруг. Переключается эфирным манипулятором.
		</note>
	</miner>
	<reprogrammer>
		<desc>
			Какой-то безумец разбросал по всему миру тёмные клетки из неизвестного материала, обычно находящиеся в булыжниковых комнатах под землёй или в крепостях ада. Их особенность в том, что каким-то образом из них бесконечно вылазят толпы монстров. Многие пытались изучить, создать аналоги этих клеток, однако эта идея оказалась провальной. Но вы смогли изобрести устройство, позволяющее изменить тип существа в клетке на другой. Это значительно ускорит добычу ценного лута.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reprogrammer>
	<repeater>
		<desc>
			Ваш первый рывок в передаче энергии стал катастрофой. Деревянные передатчики работают просто ужасно. Оглядываясь назад, можно сказать, что дерево - самый неподходящий материал для передачи энергии. Возможно, кристаллы, которые вы всегда используете, будут получше? Если дерево впитывало всю энергию, то они должны, наоборот, направлять её. Руна определённого цвета также поможет сфокусировать энергию. Однако это позволит передавать только определённый тип энергии. Возможно, в будущем вы найдёте способ исправить это.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</repeater>
	<weakrepeater>
		<desc>
			Энергия кристального пилона распространяется лишь на %d блоков вокруг, а также блокируется любым непрозрачным предметом. Вам нужен какой-то способ передавать эту энергию, ведь постоянно бегать между пилонами и обустраивать около них свои базы - не лучшая затея. И вы его нашли - люменовый передатчик. Его единтсвенный недостаток в том, что он поглощает значительную часть передаваемой энергии, поэтому желательно продумать кратчайший путь от пилона к вашей базе. Конечно, стоит учитывать, что это ваша первая попытка передать кристальную энергию, поэтому эффективность этого метода остаётся... под вопросом.
		</desc>
		<note>
			
		</note>
	</weakrepeater>
	<rift>
		<desc>
			Передача различных вещей на далёкие расстояния, будь то блоки или жидкости, занимает много времени. Эта проблема легко решаема с помощью "разлома". Благодаря определённой связи с пустотой, он может передавать предметы, жидкости, энергию и даже редстоун-сигнал куда угодно, в том числе в другие измерения.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Всегда ставится в паре.

			Что попадает в один разлом, выходит из другого с противоположенной стороны. Например, если в один разлом что-то положили с северной стороны, то из другого разлома оно выйдет с южной.

			Эфирный манипулятор позволяет указать, с какой стороны будут загружаться/выходить предметы.
		</note>
	</rift>
	<tank>
		<desc>
			Хранение предметов - не такая уж и большая проблема. Но вот хранение жидкостей - проблема намного больше. Конечно, у вас уже есть различные резервуары, но даже самые большие из них рано или поздно заполнятся. Вы нашли способ создать резервуар, который, благодаря связи с пустотой, сможет хранить непостижимое уму количество жидкости.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Ёмкость расчитывается по формуле %d*(n+3)^2 вёдер, где n - количество блоков резервуара.

			Может быть абсолютно любого размера и формы, но максимальная ёмкость ограничена %d вёдер.
		</note>
	</tank>
	<compound>
		<desc>
			Новые передатчики работают просто отлично, однако у них всё ещё есть две существенные проблемы. Первая - иногда вам приходится строить сразу несколько линий передатчиков в одном месте, что довольно затратно. Вторая - если ваша база находится не на поверхности, а, скажем, под землёй, вам придётся делать дырку в стене для каждого цвета, чтобы энергия попала в ваш дом. К счастью, вы быстро нашли решение сразу двух проблем - мультипередатчик. Несмотря на то, что он немного больше обычного, он способен одновременно передавать все 16 типов энергии. К слову, потери энергии при передаче у него немного выше, поэтому их стоит использовать скорее как узлы, реле для направления энергии внутри вашей базы.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Возможна горизонтальная постройка, используя высеченный кристаллин, вместо колонн.
		</note>
	</compound>
	<charger>
		<desc>
			Вы уже знаете, как создать кристалл, фокусирующий и направляющий энергию, но что насчёт хранения? В сыром виде, кристальная энергия слишком сильна, чтобы удерживать её в обычном кристалле. Спустя некоторое время и несколько неудачных экспериментов, вы додумались заострить углы кристалла. Удивительно, но это сработало: если заострить края и сделать специальную "рамку" для кристалла, он сфокусирует всю энергию точно в центре. Этого не было задумано, но конструкция заставляет кристалл вращаться по неизвестным причинам. Остаётся надеятся, что это никак не повредит вам и вашим исследованиям.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Хранит до %d люменов каждого цвета.
		</note>
	</charger>
	<heatlily>
		<desc>
			Как-то раз, вы решили создать ферму тростника в зимнем биоме. Всё было хорошо, пока вода вокруг не замёрзла. С одной стороны, проблема не велика. С другой - довольно раздражающая. Вы придумали цветок, растапливающий снег и лёд вокруг.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</heatlily>
	<ticker>
		<desc>
			Играясь с эссенцией времени, вам пришла идея создать прибор, ускоряющий его. Он будет полезен, например, для быстрой починки предмета или любого другого действия, требующего много времени. Осталось лишь найти способ сконцентрировать эту эссенцию в одном месте...
		</desc>
		<note>

			
		</note>
	</ticker>
	<fence>
		<desc>
			В последнее время, вам всё больше нужен какой-либо способ защитить вашу базу от полчищ монстров. Обычный забор? Скучно. Ров воды? Даже паук, размеом с корову, умудряется там плавать. Неизолированные провода? Идея хорошая, но если вы сами подойдёте близко, мало не покажется. После некоторых экспериментов с эссенцией защиты, вы создали некоторого рода барьер, пропускающий вас, но не пропускающий всех остальных.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Периметр защиты указывается с помощью реле и излучателей магического барьера.

			Каждый излучатель увеличивает урон, наносимый сущностям в периментре.
		</note>
	</fence>
	<furnace>
		<desc>
			Переплавка. Одна из самых скучных вещей, которую не получится просто игнорировать. Конечно, вы пробовали ускорить его, но чаще всего это приводило к неисправности печи. Поэтому вы придумали новую печь, которая работает не только на огне, но и на кристальной энергии.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Увеличенная производительность.

			Выдаёт в %d раза больше ресурсов.
		</note>
	</furnace>
	<laser>
		<desc>
			Свет можно сфокусировать в луч. Что мешает сделать то же самое с эссенцией? Благодаря специальным линзам, вы можете создать плотный луч энергии, дальностью до %d блоков. Каждый тип эссенции имеет свой эффект; осталось узнать, какая эссенция какому эффекту соответсвует.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</laser>
	<itemrift>
		<desc>
			Вы придумали устройство для передачи предметов на небольшое расстояние, между любыми инвентарями.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Требуется прямая видимость

			Может быть ускорен с помощью %s энергии
		</note>
	</itemrift>
	<crystal>
		<desc>
			Когда вы стали активно использовать пилоны для крафта предметов, вы заметили, что они со временем истощаются и теряют свой цвет. Со временем, они восстанавливаются, но это происходит уж ОЧЕНЬ медленно. Можно посадить несколько деревьев того же цвета вокруг, это поможет, но это всё ещё не решение проблемы. Недавно, изучая кристаллы, вы вспомнили про их фокусирующее свойство. Они, будучи застывшей эссенцией, могут неплохо ускорить перезарядку пилона. Расчёты показали, что кольцо из 8 кристаллов должно ускорить перезарядку до максимума.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</crystal>
	<infuser>
		<desc>
			Кидать обычные кристаллы в хрому - это одно. Но вот кидать очищенные кристаллы туда же - совсем другое. Похоже, они не реагируют на жидкость просто так. А что, если окружить сосуд с кристаллом бассейном хромы?
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</infuser>
	<fabricator>
		<desc>
			Вы давно подметили, что многие предметы содержат в себе следы кристальной энергии. Это заставляет задуматься, неужели всё вокруг создано из неё? Вы решили проверить это, создав устройство, собирающее энергию на лопастях и фокусирующее её в центре, создавая предмет. К сожалению, или к счастью, у вас получилось, вы создали предмет из чистой энергии. Конечно, не всё так радужно. Вы можете создавать только самые простые предметы. Также, не стоит забывать, что вам всё ещё нужен 1 предмет в качестве шаблона.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Требует %d*(%.1f*n^%d) люменов за предмет.
		</note>
	</fabricator>
	<beacon>
		<desc>
			After an unfortunate encounter with an engine intake, you have been desperately seeking a way to protect yourself from the more hazardous situations you always seem to end up in. Recalling the enormous protective power of %s crystal energy to protect, you try building a beacon that radiates the energy into the air. As long as it stays supplied with energy - not an easy task, given the large energy expenditure - you may well be impossible to kill. Hopefully this should extend to any creatures you keep around, to avoid you having to constantly replace your pets as they wander into assorted machinery.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Uses %dn^%d lumens per half-heart of damage
			Max range %d blocks
		</note>
	</beacon>
	<enchanter>
		<desc>
			Enchanting has always been a random and infurating process. Spend a week collecting experience and you might get Bane of Arthropods I, or you might be lucky enough to get Fortune III and Efficiency V off of a few levels. Rather than tear your hair out trying to spend your experience efficiently, you recall the liquid chroma, which, being concentrated experience, may allow you not only automatic enchanting, but to allow you more fine control over the actual enchantments as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Enchantment base cost: %d mB per level

			Can take an already-enchanted item to discount this cost; can be placed below the table in a "normal" enchanting room to further reduce this cost
		</note>
	</enchanter>
	<chromaflower>
		<desc>
			You may not be that guy that builds 9x9 cobblestone boxes for a house, but nonetheless your ability to make your territory visually appealing has rested more on access to fancy decorations than raw architectural design. With that in mind, you work on enhancing a lowly flower with crystal energy. The end result is certainly interesting, with its gently pulsing colors, but it may also have a functional use as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</chromaflower>
	<collector>
		<desc>
			Being able to convert and concentrate experience into chroma is one thing, but until now you have been at a loss as to how to actually do that. Fortunately for you, you stumbed upon the answer while fiddling with some crystal shards; running experience over them, either draining off yourself or pumped in in liquid form, seems to catalyze the reaction.
		</desc>
		<note>
			%d XP = 1 mB of Chroma
		</note>
	</collector>
	<brewer>
		<desc>
			Everyone loves making potions...OK, no. Between collecting a hideous red weed that seems to grow so slowly you could mine a chunk before it grew, to fiddling with arcane procedures that seem designed as a last-resort replacement for something even worse, to burning through valuable ingredients for effects that last mere minutes - and at the expense of a boosted effect too! - nobody sane enjoys this process. At the very least, maybe, you can forgo most of the process by using the energy from the crystal shards instead, making the process actually worth your time.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Standard shards yield Level I 3:00 potions
			Boosted shards yield Level II 8:00 potions
		</note>
	</brewer>
	<ritual>
		<desc>
			You have heard mention of all these special abilities you can gain by imbuing yourself with large quantities of crystal energy, but you need some means to carry out the infusion. After an incident that shall never be mentioned again - and if anyone asks, no, you do not have anything to do with the crater where that village used to be - you recall the shards' infusion process. If it worked for items, maybe it will work for you as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</ritual>
	<table>
		<desc>
			Wooden crafting tables, useful as they are, have their limitations. To that end, you have found a way to affix crystal plating to a table, allowing it to store and process crystal energy, this allowing you to craft items that require magical interaction. Hopefully this one will turn out better than your other design, given that this one is not asking you to surround it with skulls or face the consequences of lightning, explosions, and noxious purple gas. You are initially unfamiliar with the table, precluding advanced use, but as you grow accustomed to it, you can be more adventurous.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</table>
	<itemcollector>
		<desc>
			Despite your best attempts, you have not been able to totally avert the need for farming, and your mountain of grey seeds and beige goo can attest to that. Unfortunately, farms tend to scatter items far and wide, leading to the need for either powerful item collection systems - which have their own problems - or a problem with so many items on the ground you find it hard to move. The item collector at last is an answer to this problem, being able to collect items anywhere in its range as soon as they are created.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Max Range: +/- %d blocks horizontally, one fourth of that vertically
		</note>
	</itemcollector>
	<aishutdown>
		<desc>
			Animal farms are an eternal headache. Between cows' endless noise and chickens' tendency to get out of any enclosure you try to keep them in, you would gleefully exterminate every one of them if not for the fact that you need a supply of leather, feathers, wool, and meat. If there was some way to stun them, to freeze their thought processes, this would probably help a great deal.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aishutdown>
	<aspect>
		<desc>
			Aside from their use as impromptu musical instruments, those jars of colored liquids you get when melting down random items have an actual use; When you decided to pursue another branch of magic, you found yourself in need of endless numbers of them. The problem is, the process of melting items into raw essentia is slow and hard to automate. With your knowledge of crystal energy, however, you have finally made a device capable of collecting crystal energy and converting it into essentia, though not exactly cheaply.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aspect>
	<lamp>
		<desc>
			The standard method of keeping unwanted creatures away is to light the area, but that is often difficult or ugly to do, and the best designs can be rendered worthless with one block left a bit too dark. With that in mind, you seek to concentrate crystal energy, being luminous itself, in some sort of lamp to keep the mobs at bay.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Range: %d for each element in the lamp, added via shards
		</note>
	</lamp>
	<powertree>
		<desc>
			Even with power crystals in place, pylons still remain incapable of handling very heavy load. That, combined with the tedium of venturing to them every time you need to recharge yourself, leads you to dream of a way to store energy in larger quantities, effectively a battery. Obviously a simple box would not be the correct approach, but maybe if you built some sort of structure, it could grow organically. As long as the energy remains pure...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Capacity: %d+%dn^%d, where n is the number of leaf blocks
			Cannot function without a view of the sky
		</note>
	</powertree>
	<lampcontrol>
		<desc>
			You often find yourself in need of controllable lighting, but redstone, even when you figured out how to alloy it into iron and stick it on the ceiling, is clumsy and requires false floors and ceiling in order to hide unslightly wiring. However, the magic aura, which you can control, may allow you to manipulate many separate lamps at a distance, obviating that need.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Max Range: %d
			Max Channel: %d
			Can be controlled manually, with redstone, by the charge state of an RF battery, or with shaft power
		</note>
	</lampcontrol>
	<aspectjar>
		<desc>
			This fabrication process is a nightmare. It is incredibly unstable - having exploded, sent items flying, hit you with lightning, and more - and worse yet needs liquid essence out of jars, which, having a small capacity, constantly necessitate tedious filling. Being able to store more in a jar - perhaps even multiple types! - would be of enormous convenience. However, storing essentia in this way seems to have broken the ability of some of your devices to draw from it at a distance; fortunately, things that use tubes (or their replacements) do still work. Perhaps you will find a way to restore full functionality later.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Primal Aspect Capacity: %d
			Other Aspect Capacity: %d
		</note>
	</aspectjar>
	<farmer>
		<desc>
			Harvesting crops is somewhat of a hassle. Doing it manually is extremely slow and ineffective, and those fans you used, while they work, are loud and tend to send items flying. Channelling nature-based energy is likely to provide a superior solution.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</farmer>
	<automator>
		<desc>
			Though less of a hassle than some other fabrication systems - that pyramidal altar nearly left you dead on the table - your casting system can still be tedious, particularly with recursive crafting that can take quite a bit of time. You DID create a device for placing items in stands automatically, but it is slow, limited to a few recipes, and cannot actually start the crafting, meaning you are still forced to be involved. This is where an idea hits you - you should be familiar enough with some of these recipes that you might be able to build on that device, adding what is missing and finally achieving proper automation.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</automator>
	<biomepainter>
		<desc>
			Too often you find yourself in need of tweaking the climate around you, often because some task you are working on requires specific temperatures or humidities (those bees you were working on proved particularly inflexible). It is not too much of a stretch to imagine that you might be able to use crystal energy to accomplish that task, and on top of that make it as easy as painting on a canvas.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</biomepainter>
	<medistributor>
		<desc>
			That digitial storage system of yours is unmatched in its convenience, except for one thing. Though it has a special device for pumping out items, and another for using internal item buffers to control a redstone signal, doing this with multiple items quickly becomes infeasible. To that end, you have designed an assembly that can function as several of these in parallel, allowing you to always maintain certain item levels in the system.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</medistributor>
	<rfdistributor>
		<desc>
			You thought that it could hardly get any easier with this kind of power; simply hook up the conduits from a generator to a machine and everything worked. However, you were still presented with one final dilemma: When grouping machines together, the cluster of cables is both unsightly and inconvenient to navigate around. Some way to transmit that power wirelessly from above would solve this problem.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</rfdistributor>
	<fluiddistributor>
		<desc>
			Noting the similarity between this red-tinted magic power and the way fluids tend to flow - one would almost think they were designed by the same person - you figure: If you can make one to radiate the power, surely you can make one to radiate fluid as well.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</fluiddistributor>
	<window>
		<desc>
			Some say a special kind of window exists, one that should you gaze into it, might just find that the view on the other side becomes your reality.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a square frame of crystal-based stone, such as crystalline stone, shielding stone, or obsidian, and to be linked to another location
		</note>
	</window>
	<music>
		<desc>
			How many times have you banged out a tune on the different colors of crystals? With your new device, you should be able to attain even greater musical fidelity, complete with greater range, chord capability, and even - somehow - an oddly familiar melody that came pre-etched into the crystal matrix.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Can be connected to a repeater network to play the repeaters with the music; place on top of Nether Quartz or Crystalline Stone

			Place on top of Nether Quartz to broadcast the sound
		</note>
	</music>
	<turret>
		<desc>
			If you had an emerald for every time a creeper ambushed you right as you left your front door, you would have enough to be able to afford trading with villagers. Frustrated with this repeated occurrence, you have designed a small construct which can fire energy into nearby hostiles, ultimately killing them. Now all they need is a high-pitched voice and a polite demeanor...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a clear view of the sky and the target mob to function
			Can be upgraded with different runes below it
		</note>
	</turret>
	<pylonturbo>
		<desc>
			You knew you could turbocharge your pylons, but that little display of yours, hopping up and down around the pylon, wildly flailing your manipulator, was neither insightful, productive, nor dignified. Now, however, the pattern is more clear: You need to enhance the structure, building a ring of 8 foci - and one central one below the pylon itself - and trigger the central one with your manipulator. Surely interrupting this process - or breaking the stabilization ring afterwards - is a very bad idea.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Ring: Requires a clear view of the sky and air around it to work; Center: Must be placed 8 blocks below the pylon's orb
		</note>
	</pylonturbo>
	<personal>
		<desc>
			<!-- Flying out to each of the sixteen colors of pylon to draw energy from them to power your abilities is a massive headache. Perhaps you could try to imitate them somehow. No doubt you lack the skill - or patience - required to duplicate them exactly, but the end result, if not able to be networked, might still serve as a useful charging point, as well as a nice decoration. -->
			Ever since you first started discovering and making use of the pylons, basically every person you have met has cracked some joke about how you should construct more of them. If you could do THAT, you would have already done so, not still be wasting time flying out to the ones you found so as to charge yourself off of them. Perhaps another attempt at an imitation for charging purposes is in order...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</personal>
	<cloaking>
		<desc>
			Rather inconveniently, you have found yourself largely confined to your base during the night, as it is your only defence against the waves of mobs, which lock onto you the moment you step outside. And this is not counting the time a horde of zombies, detecting the light of your constructions, made a beeline to you and destroyed most of the structure that stood in their way. After much frustration, it hit you: A cloaking device, which makes you undetectable unless at point-blank range. Pleasantly, it even smells of raspberries.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires the tower structure around it to focus its energy and function correctly
		</note>
	</cloaking>
	<lighter>
		<desc>
			Caves are an extremely unpleasant place to be - how many times have you found a large vein of ore, only to be shot into lava, fall down a gravel pit, or be dive-bombed by a creeper? - largely due to their cavernous gloom. Sure, you can cover the entire interior of the cave system with torches, but that quickly gets ridiculous, and after that incident with a gas pocket near the coal vein you wish for an alternative. Knowing that %s energy is that of light, you are sure you can use that to your advantage and make cave-mining actually enjoyable again.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</lighter>
	<reverter>
		<desc>
			Your world is slowly becoming corrupted. From pillars of obsidian that darken the world around them, to a purple weed that overtakes everything in sight, you find the once-beautiful landscape becoming ugly and inhospitable. Even the magic forests spread by the trees often make a mess of the biome. What you really need is a way to restore the biome to its former state.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</reverter>
	<cobblegen>
		<desc>
			You never think you would run out of cobblestone...until you actually do. Sure, you could mine more out of the ground, but you have better things to occupy your time. You know that mixing water and lava will make cobblestone, but automating that process is messy and often costly. One solution would be a flower that would pull up the required liquid from nearby pools, mixing it and dropping the result. It might even be able to make things other than cobblestone given the correct input liquids.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cobblegen>
	<plantaccel>
		<desc>
			Like the proverbial grass and its glacial growth speed, your various flowers and plants to improve the area around them operate at a very slow pace. Perhaps they could be improved upon by being planted on a plant of its own.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</plantaccel>
	<cropspeed>
		<desc>
			Though some crops grow rapidly, the majority - even after careful crossbreeding and hours digging up weeds - very much do not. Already available to you are various means with which to increase that speed, but none of them fit neatly into the farm area itself, instead often requiring being placed nearby. This of course introduces an efficiency penalty, one that would be very desirable to avoid.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</cropspeed>
	<inserter>
		<desc>
			You have repeatedly found yourself manually adding items to constructs that cannot be connected to normal item transport. You long ago tired of dropping stack after stack of sugar into a stone basin, or of berries into a puddle of chroma. You need a way to automate that process before you give up and find something less of a hassle to work with.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Link to a location with the linking tool

			Redstone input to a side disables the corresponding slot
		</note>
	</inserter>
	<essentiarelay>
		<desc>
			So you have a cauldron full of water, in which you need to dump various ingredients to fabricate your desired target. As that process more often fails than not, producing copious amounts of noxious gas in the process, you created an odd construct to help automate the process. However, you need to actually transport the essentia there, and the piping you tried at first...leaves much to be desired. A longer-range and more flexible solution - ideally more consistently functional as well - would fare far better. Simply attach one to each end, as well as some at regular intervals in between.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Will continuously attempt to fill labelled jars and empty alembics

			Also expands the range of the Infusion Matrix aspect source search
		</note>
	</essentiarelay>
	<glowfire>
		<desc>
			Some things you never have enough of, in particular diamonds, shards, and iron (the last of which was not helped by your attempts to build a turbine the size of a small house). Other things you have so much of that your biggest problem is storing it somewhere. What would be most convenient would be to be able to decompose the latter into energy with which you could cast the former. Surely nothing could go wrong with this sort of exchange project...
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</glowfire>
	<broadcast>
		<desc>
			You now regret living in a mountain archipelago. For one, most of the pylons to which you wish to connect are thousands of meters away. Worse, though, are that many are across vast stretches of ocean. Yes, you could build cobblestone pillars to raise repeaters from the ocean floor, but you want a solution that is both convenient and does not look ridiculous. To that end, you designed high-power broadcasters, which can send energy over thousands of blocks. However, such power requires a large structure, and that they would interfere if too close to each other.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</broadcast>
	<enchantdecomp>
		<desc>
			Rather starving, you made a box of netting and wood and plopped it in a pond, hoping to catch fish over time. However, the world is apparently determined to see you starve, as all you have obtained is an endless series of - weakly - enchanted bows and boots. They are too close to the end of their life to be useful, but the weak magic of the enchantments might be able to be put to good use.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</enchantdecomp>
	<lumenwire>
		<desc>
			You took three steps into a ruined, overgrown stone structure deep in the jungle and were rewarded with an arrow to the face. Primitive as they might be, tripwires are an effective trap or other detector. However, they are just that - primitive. Not all constructions are amenable to redstone connectivity, and you would far prefer something a bit more visually appealing.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</lumenwire>
	<particles>
		<desc>
			Almost every construct you make seems to give off clouds of glowing particles. Given their visual appeal, it would be quite pleasant to be able to summon them at will, especially if able to control their appearance.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</particles>
	<meteor>
		<desc>
			Lumen turrets are all well and good, but they need to be spammed to protect a large area, and do not work for areas without a clear sky view. You tried a magnetic projectile launcher earlier, but for what it accomplished in mob-killing it doubled in destroying the base you were trying to protect. To that end, you have decided to create a defense tower, one that can attack mobs at a large range, and doing large amounts of splash damage. Now, some towers are more effective than others against certain mob types (in case you hadn't noticed), and this one does not work for fliers.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Comes in three tiers, each with greater capabilities and costs.
		</note>
	</meteor>
	<fluxcreator>
		<desc>
			Every time you screw up with a crucible, or a jar of magic...stuff, it creates a cloud or puddle of purple goo. Now, you are SUPPOSED to be unhappy about this, but who could be unhappy about a supply of pretty purple...stuff? Sure, others will say that you are crazy - or, more than they already do - but since when has that stopped you?
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</fluxcreator>
	<villagerepair>
		<desc>
			Villagers may LOOK intelligent (ok, not really), but after their crowning architectural achievement was a pylon embedded in their wall and their attempt at a casting structure was about as skillful as a painting made with one's rear, it is clear that their cognitive capabilites are more like that of the carrots they farm. That extends to their defence strategies during a zombie seige, which consist of trying to cram the entire village into a tiny hut and usually forgetting to close the door. Sure, you could try teaching them, but after all they got out of your last educational session (about early discoveries you made) was "LEAF"...well...good luck with that.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</villagerepair>
	<wireless>
		<desc>
			You are already very familiar with the fact that certain constructs require energy. Most draw that energy directly off the repeater network, and some use the relay system. However, others seem to need to be in proximity to a node of sorts, which weakly radiates energy around it. It even appears to be capable of passing through solid barriers, though it unsuprisingly is rather less efficient when it does.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Can be built on a %s to broadcast power to other %ss
		</note>
	</wireless>
	<areabreaker>
		<desc>
			For some reason, you decided that the bulk of your home would be underground. That of course means clearing away the rock, gravel, and other materials in the way, and this presents something of a problem. You could spent hours whacking at the rock with a pickaxe, hammer, or other tool, but that is a waste of your time. You have in the past tried a mechanical device to clear areas, but it was only capable of rectangular areas, and worse it destroyed the minerals in its target volume (or, with modification, yielded the materials, but then left orange piping all over the room). You need another alternative.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires a redstone signal
		</note>
	</areabreaker>
	<teleport>
		<desc>
			Being the prudent designer you are, you have decided to split your base into multiple structures spread across the landscape. However, this created a problem: Simply getting to them becomes something of a chore. However, another idea occurs to you: You could build a link of sorts, a gate, at any number of locations and be able to link between any two points at will. As long as the purity of the link is maintained, the two gates should work in harmony, and the supremacy of this method of travel will act as an emancipation from your current commute.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Can be toggled into private mode (purple), as well as between arrival/departure only (red/yellow).

			GUI Color Statuses: White = Available; Red = Owned by Other; Yellow = Unpowered; Magenta = No Structure; Blue = Other Dimension
		</note>
	</teleport>
	<harvestplant>
		<desc>
			Flowers. You cannot get enough of them, especially ones that come in 16 colors. However, though you have the ability to create them using nothing but raw magic, harvesting them automatically has proven somewhat more difficult. On the advice of someone else, you made a drum and started banging on it with the same magic used to summon the flowers. Though it worked, your tree farm and crops nearby were also affected, causing you to revert to the loud and space-consuming piston and water contraptions. Now it finally hits you: You are planting flowers; a flower might be used to harvest as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Checks the flowers adjacent to it to know what to break
		</note>
	</harvestplant>
	<alveary>
		<desc>
			Untold piles of wax, jelly, and pollen later, and now poorer some 27 drums of honey, you finally have it: The pinnacle of your apiculture abilities, large structures to keep your bees as happy as possible and to maximize their productivity (wooden boxes, treated or not, proved lacking in that regard). And they help, but you still want MORE. More speed, more products, more capabilities. So an idea occurs to you: Lumen-powered bees! Well, more accurately, using the lumen energy to enhance their capabilities, or of the housing itself. You might even be able to plug it into those crystal relays from that glowy sparky thing you made as well.
		</desc>
		<note>
			%s
		</note>
	</alveary>
	<fluidrelay>
		<desc>
			Fluids. Fluids EVERYWHERE. Water, lava, oil, honey, liquid nitrogen, cryotheum, and more, routed all over your base with a rat's nest of pipes and ducts. Sure, some of them can be hidden in walls or the floor, but it is still a pain to connect everything, and that time you accidentally disconnected a fluid line and half your base cratered itself remains painfully sharp in your memory. Though you obviously will still need to connect all the endpoints, there has to be a better way...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Positive pressures try to push fluids, negative pressures try to pull
		</note>
	</fluidrelay>
	<bookdecomp>
		<desc>
			So you can create world after world by scribbling in a book, but you can even do this without writing much at all, and some unseen balancing force appears to fill in the missing pieces (though sometimes it appears to take issue with your choices). And few things are more frustrating than creating a random world and seeing it has a trait you want but lack the means to manually specify. You want those symbols, and you are going to get them out of those books any way you can.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</bookdecomp>
	<routerhub>
		<desc>
			So you have a field of constructs, all generating or needing items. Sure, you could run a giant grid of item pipes, but that is boring, expensive, and ugly. What you want is the ability to connect them all through the aether to some central hub which would automatically pull and push items as necessary.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Endpoints must be connected to the hub (by right-clicking) in order to be placed
		</note>
	</routerhub>
	<avolaser>
		<desc>
			Avolite crystals are ancient and imbued with magical power...You think. With that in mind, you have constructed a housing to focus and project that energy in an impressive and violent display. Ancient temples might not be able to maintain a security system this deadly, but you certainly can.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</avolaser>
	<focuscrystal>
		<desc>
			Crafting things can be painfully slow, and you are not all that keen on starting the process then wandering away to do other things, forgetting about the crafting almost immediately. If you could focus the pulses and bursts of energies used by the constructs into a more coherent...beam, to overcharge them and make them more efficient, you would better distribute the power within them and probably enhance the charge rate as well. No longer will you need to dwell around your construct doing nothing but waiting.
		</desc>
		<note>
			More refined crystals yield more powerful effects
			Up to 8 crystals per construct
		</note>
	</focuscrystal>
	<chromacrafter>
		<desc>
			As powerful as some of your constructs have proven, crafting them has been at times painful enough that you have mentally prepended the ingredient's names with some variant of an expletive. In particular has been the various alloy ingots, which are not exactly expensive but whose particularly finicky and easy-to-disrupt nature of crafting has made you dread their production, to say nothing of their unified compound. If only you could mix them all together in a shielded glass tank or something, though you would need to find a way to have it fit more than one block of fluid...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Consumes three buckets of chroma per crafting cycle
		</note>
	</chromacrafter>
	<fluxmaker>
		<desc>
			This purple goo you get when you @#!$ up is supposed to be a problem, as if you were being punished, but in truth a vibrant purple liquid or gas could be nothing else than a pretty reward. To the shock and horror of your acquaintances, you have embarked on a quest to obtain more of it. Some stacks of cobblestone into a vat later, you have a purple mess that spawns similarly-colored slimes, but this is not going to help you decorate with it. You need a more organized solution.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</fluxmaker>
	<functionrelay>
		<desc>
			Certain constructs have areas of effect that is difficult to work with, making you now somewhat regret your decision to build a terrace farm whose contours make the placement of any such device rather awkward. One solution would be to create some sort of relay, that would be placed in the primary construct's area of effect and which would delegate said effect to its own more workable region.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</functionrelay>
	<multibuilder>
		<desc>
			For some applications, you find yourself needing to build either a structure consisting of a repeating unit, or multiple orderly-arranged multiblocks. Either case has generally proven tedious, as there is only so much enjoyment to be had in placing the same ten blocks over and over (and over and over and over) again. Your first attempt with a wooden axe proved utterly fruitless - whoever claimed it has magic capabilities is clearly about as sane as a house made of TNT - so what you may want to try is to mirror your actions when you build or break blocks.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Interacting with a manipulator changes region size; empty hand changes cell count or region shape
		</note>
	</multibuilder>
	<explosionshield>
		<desc>
			You found a way to convert between that magic fluidlike power and a more mechanical variant, a...manafetic...malgetonatic...macta...whatever. However, they require coolant, and when you tried to use them, your supply of said coolant apparently proved insufficient, as what you returned to was less a house and more a field of craters. You COULD hunt down the designer and leave them an immature rant, complaining about how they ruined your base, but a more dignified solution would be some sort of...shield. Something that, while it may not save the engines themselves, will prevent them from destroying their surroundings.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</explosionshield>
	<aurapoint>
		<desc>
			Upon completing the restorative ritual, the glowing central point transformed itself, into a much more luminous...something. Having finally brought it back home - after inadvertently destroying one on a previous attempt, forgetting to use an enchanted pick - you have determined that it has multiple properties, including defence and imbuing the surrounding area with a large boost in fertility. You have also learned it does not terribly appreciate being moved.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</aurapoint>
	<manabooster>
		<desc>
			Pools of shiny blue liquid and flowers that eat cake, leaves, bread, and coal to make said liquid are nice, as are ones that turn this blue liquid into clay, item movement, dungeon loot, or forbidden knowledge. But there comes a time when you realize that in order to fully supply those flowers (disregarding the sunflower field that now looks more like a radiation accident), you need enough flowers and their preferred foods that you can barely move. Additionally, even the best spreaders can barely manage the load. What you need is something else which can pull from the flowers with a much greater efficiency.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</manabooster>
	<progresslink>
		<desc>
			Sharing a base with a friend is a common practice, but you have found that what you learn as you explore and experiment is less easily shared. You could of course have your partner perform the same actions as you, but they may be more interested in pulling up ores, playing bee matchmaker, or going insane by reading ancient scribbles. Or they may be interested but unable to learn, preferring to watch crops grow or to fall into lava. Either way, if you could make it such that the two - or more - of you learned in tandem, this problem would be solved.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires that both players have similar progression at the time of linking
			If the two players have different progression, the other will be made to match, possibly forgetting some of their progression

			Both players are still required to be involved for some progress
		</note>
	</progresslink>
	<optimizer>
		<desc>
			More often than not, the path energy takes from pylons to your constructs looks less like a route and more like the random wanderings of a chicken. This would not matter, were it not for the fact that the less direct paths lead to less efficient transfer of said energy, and thus a greater load on your pylons. After a number of attempts, some of which ended in puddles or fountains of goo, you have finally devised a construct that can optimize the energy flow in your network.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</optimizer>
	<injector>
		<desc>
			Despite having only recently begun using casting stands to enhance your table, you are thoroughly sick of stuffing items into them; those recipes involving shoving shards together in various combinations have proven particularly tedious. Some time ago, you designed a construct for placing items in devices; perhaps you could apply that knowledge and design something capable of being given a recipe and placing the ingredients in the stands automatically. That does not quite automate the process - you still need to place the central item, and trigger the actual crafting - but it is a start.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Can only produce intermediate products
		</note>
	</injector>
	<landmark>
		<desc>
			Apparently sticking blue dye on a power torch, beyond simply tinting it that color, makes it, when used with others like it, capable of demarcating an area or volume which can then be used by some of your machinery. Useful, perhaps, but they retain their parent torch's need to be stuck onto something, and the bounds are not always clear. You can solve both of those issues by binding them into the world somewhat more explicitly...something you have perhaps managed to do somewhat TOO effectively.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</landmark>
	<hoverpad>
		<desc>
			Having built a base with a large number of rooms spread across multiple floors, and a maze of stairs and walkways between them, you have realized that while it excels in aesthetics, it suffers greatly in practicality. In an attempt to solve this, you created an access shaft allowing you to travel between any two floors. However, this too has an issue: Reliably getting between said floors, with nothing solid to walk on, is fiddly and requires the ability to fly. If you could just...suppress gravity and friction while moving through the shaft, it would be far more useful.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</hoverpad>
	<deathfog>
		<desc>
			Below the world lurks some sort of...THING. A distortion, a corruption, of the fabric of the world itself. Spending time in proximity to it, in addition to being deeply unsettling, is actively dangerous; it seems to infect its nearby surroundings and literally suck the life out of whatever creatures happen to be near. Perhaps if you could somehow 'sample' this entity, you could find a way to capitalize on that sort of effect for your own purposes. Of course, the first thing to work out will be whether you can restrict the effect to only harming creatures you actually wish to hurt.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</deathfog>
	<voidtrap>
		<desc>
			You have finally determined a way to destroy that evil distortion, the way it has done to you so many times. And indeed, you will be turning its own nature against it, making for a healthy dose of irony. However, in order to actually initiate the whole process, you need to build and then activate a large construct, something not easily done if the thing is there and denying you the ability to linger in the area. Additionally, you will need a way to trap it within range of the construct, so that your purification process can actually act upon it. This device may be the key to both problems.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Requires setup in both the overworld and whatever dimension the ritual is performed
		</note>
	</voidtrap>
	<playerinfuser>
		<desc>
			Having found a new way to directly imbue significant quantities of chroma into shards, you wonder if you could apply that same sort of strategy with your own body. In particular, it would be useful to use this infusion to enhance your body's ability to store energy, thus allowing you to carry more around at any time. Obviously, this will require refinements to the construct, but it should not necessitate a total redesign.
		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</playerinfuser>
	<smelterydistributor>
		<desc>
			As you develop your tools, you have needed a large brick basin in which you can melt down various metals and then taps to pour it into various casts. That last step is where the headaches begun; the taps are stupidly slow, and the piping you have access to achieved nothing remotely resembling success. Copper/lead pipes blew up in your face; ones of stone and glass developed a hopeless mix of random crap and clogged completely. And should the metal run out, none of them are able to avoid filling a cast only partway, leaving you with six half-casted ingots you can make zero use of. @#!$ this, you need your own solution.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Prioritizes tool casts over everything, and basins over all other casts
		</note>
	</smelterydistributor>
	<launchpad>
		<desc>
			It may look nice to have a large tower or other similar elevation change in your constructions, but in practical terms traversing that difference is simply a headache. Getting down is simple enough - drop down a shaft and hope to avoid becoming a wet smear - but getting up is rather more problematic. You tried a whole array of solutions, ranging from a gem imbued with magic flower energy to a pile of slime goo to various levitation constructs to even a simple jetpack, but none of them work easily, cheaply, and quickly, without requiring you rummage through your bag of tools. As is becoming routine, innovation will be required.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Will not fire for players who are sneaking

			Can be enhanced with a ring of liquid ender
		</note>
	</launchpad>
	<toolstorage>
		<desc>
			Nearly every chest you find is likely to have some kind of tool inside, every single one with different durability or enchantments. Having raided a few dozen such structures, and obtained yet more tools from various mobs, you have 247 kinds of gold sword alone and more bronze helmets than you care to count. The usual solution of digitization would need a whole wall of storage drives just for iron pickaxes, given a 63-type limit you have never managed to exceed, and even a filing cabinet stuffed with tools rapidly exceeds capacity, not to mention taking forever to search through. Perhaps you can design something better.
		</desc>
		<note>
			Storage modes:

			%s
		</note>
	</toolstorage>
	<beestorage>
		<desc>
			The limitations of that digital storage system's ability to handle many discrete forms of items have become troublesome once again. As soon as you delved into breeding bees, trees, and butterflies, you were quickly inundated with products in every genetic combination conceivable. Not helping is the time your butterfly enclosure sprung a leak and the escapees proceeded to cross-pollinate every tree and plant in sight. Two dozen storage drives for Apple Oak pollen alone is not acceptable, but on the bright side, you have encountered a similar problem to this before, and might have something of a solution...
		</desc>
		<note>
			Stores any variants of one "species format" like pollen, princesses, or larvae
		</note>
	</beestorage>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
	<name>
		<desc>

		</desc>
		<note>

		</note>
	</name>
</machines>
